<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logs on len.to</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/zensurgery/log/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logs on len.to</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 12:12:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/zensurgery/log/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Validating Generated HTML</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zensurgery/log/validating-generated-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 12:12:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zensurgery/log/validating-generated-html/</guid>
      <description>I ran this website through an HTML validator and discovered it was missing some closing &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt; tags. Tracking these errors down can be challenging with generated HTML, so I decided to add linting to the build process and catch problems early.&#xA;The Nu HTML Checker I used above conveniently ships a Docker image containing a CLI called vnu. I ran into two small challenges integrating vnu in the multi-stage build:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Favicons 🤔</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zensurgery/log/emoji-favicons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zensurgery/log/emoji-favicons/</guid>
      <description>Turns out SVG can draw images from text and is a valid favicon format supported by most major browsers.&#xA;Here&amp;rsquo;s how it works Create a favicon.svg file. There are a lot of opinions on what size(s) to make your favicon, but modern browsers support a 32x32 icon so we&amp;rsquo;ll use that. Just set the font-size to 32 and offset the y axis by the same amount, so the icon is visible:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Asset Delivery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zensurgery/log/optimizing_assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 20:47:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zensurgery/log/optimizing_assets/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to improve the CSS and JavaScript portions of this website for a while. The main items I want to address are:&#xA;Removing JavaScript from HTML templates Find a better way to inject site content into JavaScript Bundle all CSS into a single file Minify and fingerprint CSS and JavaScript I initially intended to plug various CSS and JavaScript processing tools into the Docker build pipeline, but that quickly spiraled out of control when npm got involved.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
